# Conner McCown

Passionate, results-driven leader with a demonstrated history of 6 years of software implementation, client management, employee training, reporting, creating as well as maintaining long-lasting relationships. I'm an excellent communicator with an aptitude for identifying and solving technical problems.

4758 S Apple Cross Way Salt Lake City, UT 84107 (435) 862-0275 connersmccown@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **GBS Benefits,** Salt Lake City, UT— Online Implementation Manager

June 2019 - Present

- Oversee the day to day operations of multiple implementations.
- Perform quality assurance checks on all finished implementations.
- Hold weekly project meetings to track and report on progress.
- Collect, identify and implement client data into HR Employee benefit software (Employee Navigator).
- Collaborate with upper management to create and implement processes that streamline the implementation process.
- Receive and respond to various client issues/questions in a timely manner.
- Act as point of contact for team members when an escalated issue
- Provide comprehensive training for new team members.
- Manage and prepare billing reports monthly for clients.

## Paramount Acceptance, Holladay, UT— Account Executive

June 2015 - June 2019

- Developed and maintained strong business relationships with new and existing accounts.
- Successful track record of onboarding/implementing new accounts
- Provide ongoing in depth training both on-site and via web demos.

### **SKILLS**

**Project Management** 

Microsoft Office, Excel

Javascript

Node.JS

**API Integration** 

CSS/Bootstrap/Bulma

HTML

Team Management

Software Implementation

**Customer Service** 

Account Management

Team Player

Leadership

Software Implementation

## **EDUCATION**

**University of Utah Coding Bootcamp,** Salt Lake City, UT — Full Stack Web Development

January 2022 - Present